### Madhumita Gore

+91 7020989294 | goremadhumita@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/madhumitagore

# **Summary:**

A self-driven and detail-oriented HR professional with 7+ years of experience in IT, Ed-Tech, e-learning, Landscaping and PMC/construction/interior fit out sectors in a variety of HR functions with a particular emphasis on recruitment.

Also worked on onboarding, exit process, payroll, performance management, training and development, background checks, and administrative tasks. Reliable and well-organized team player with strong communication and interpersonal skills.

# Work Experience:

# Aptara New Media Pvt. Ltd., Pune, India (Sept 2023-till date)

Senior Executive Human Resources

- Handle end to end recruitment.
- Lead and mentor a team.
- Stakeholder management.
- Process standardization and improvisation for various HR activities.
- Coordinate with vendors for employee background verification and adhere to the timeline
- Conduct a reference check of a candidate before joining.
- Conduct survey for new joiners to understand their on boarding and induction experience.
- Analyze the results and develop an action plan.
- Ensure on time weekly progress reports & ad hoc reports.

#### Rayden Interactive (NowPhreesia) Pune, India (June 2021-Aug 2023)

Analyst, Talent Acquisition/ Recruiter

- Coordinate with the hiring managers to identify hiring needs and candidate selection criteria.
- Create job description and interview questions specific to the position.
- Design a scorecard as per hiring need.
- Source applicants through LinkedIn, Naukri, referral and other channels.
- Conduct preliminary interviews with potential candidates.
- Negotiate and release the offer.
- Maintain reports- daily, weekly, and monthly and ensure timely updates to the US stakeholders.
- Ensure the selected candidate completes the documentation process before joining.
- Draft& update SOP's related to recruitment process and train the new joiners.
- Collaborated with the HR operations team for Zoho Recruit ATS Implementation.

# BYJU'S (Think & Learn Pvt. Ltd.) (April 2021-June 2021)

Unit People Partner

- SPOC for the employees based out of the allocated locations.
- Ensure best-in-class on boarding experience.
- Upon candidate joining, provide accurate process information as per the designed policies.
- Coordinate with the corporate office for issuing various HR letters.
- Ensure timely input of attendance data for computation of salary.
- Handle grievances and employee queries.
- Ensure proper process adherence with regards to exit management.

### AMs Project Consultants Pvt. Ltd, Pune, India (June 2017-April 2021)

**HR** Executive

- Handle entire recruitment life cycle.
- Ensure smooth onboarding and documentation of new hires.
- Assist in payroll & PF process by coordinating with the Finance team.
- Assist in employee performance review and appraisal.
- Conduct employment verification of new joiners.
- Collaborate with Managers to identify training need and develop the training program.
- Assist in grievance resolution.
- Issue various HR documents.
- Implement Keka HRMS as a part of HR automation project.
- Update records & maintain documents of employees on HR portal.
- Respond to employee queries.
- Maintain office supplies inventory.
- Make the necessary travel arrangements.
- Coordinate with IT for assets for new hires & manage vendor.
- Attendance, Leave Management & Exit Management.

#### **Education:**

Master of Business Administration (HR) (Savitribai Phule Pune University)	-	2017
Bachelor of Business Administration (HR) (Savitribai Phule Pune University)	-	2015

### **Tools/Skills:**

HRMS Implementation (Zoho Recruit, Keka)

Job Portals (LinkedIn, Naukri)

ATS (Talentpool, Zoho, Workday)

MS Office

### **Certification:**

- Excel with LinkedIn Recruiter Assessment 2023 (LinkedIn Learning)
- Generative AI in HR 2024 (LinkedIn Learning)
- Technical Recruiting 2024 (LinkedIn Learning)

#### Languages:

English Hindi Marathi

Recommendation:

# Pankti Chauhan HR Manager (AMs Project Consultants Pvt. Ltd.)

"Madhumita is one of the most dedicated professional I've worked with. She is focused, reliable & goal oriented. She is kind and out of box thinker and knows how to bring best out of each person. I was blessed to have her in my team. She is an asset to any company."

Link <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/madhumitagore/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/madhumitagore/</a>

# Maj. Puneet Arora (Retd) Executive Director (AMs Project Consultants Pvt. Ltd.)

"There are very few people whom I have come across in almost three decades of experience, who are enthusiastic, have a positive energy every day, are willing to carry on with there task and alongside, they are also willing to help people when they approach with even mundane issues. Madhumita is one such person. Hard working and dedicated to her work, Madhumita is an asset for any organisation."

Link <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/madhumitagore/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/madhumitagore/</a>